A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz, General Administration, Series 5 FA818
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Administration, 1958-1979; 5; 55 Cubic Feet 125 boxes.
  - Food Service - General File 1, 1970; 1 of 4 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Food Service - General File 2, 1970-1971; 2 of 4 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Food Service - General File 1, 1972; 3 of 4 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Food Service - General File 1, 1973; 4 of 4 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Food Service - General, 1974-1978 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Food Services: Revenue Totals, 1971-1973; 1 of 2 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Food Services: Revenue Totals, 1973-1974; 2 of 2 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Food Services: Schrafft Food Services, Inventories, 1971; 1 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Food Services: Schrafft Food Services, Inventories, 1971-1972; 2 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Food Services: Special Functions (prior to Schrafft contract), 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Food Services: Special Functions (File I from date of Schrafft contract), 1 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Food Services: Special Functions (File I from date of Schrafft contract), 1972; 2 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Food Services: Special Functions (File II from date of Schrafft contract), 1972-1973; 1 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Food Services: Special Functions (File II from date of Schrafft contract), 1973-1974; 2 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Food Service: Working File - C. E. Sunderlin, 1973-1974; 1 of 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Food Service: Working File - C. E. Sunderlin, 1974-1976; 2 of 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Ford Foundation - regarding Development Program, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Formal Contract Signing, 1973 November 27 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Foundation General Information I, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Foundation General Information, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Foundation Proposals - R. W. Johnson and Kresge, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Fringe Benefits, 1973-1977 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Gershinowitz Unitrust, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Glassblower Shop, 1972-1977 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Gold, A., 1971 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Committee on Scholastic Achievement, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Fellows, 1955-General Information, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Graduate fellows: Special Advances, 1956-1972 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Fellows, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Students: General, 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Students: General, 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Students: Fellowship Stipends, 1958-1975 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Students General II, 1972-1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Study Brochure, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Grant Applications and Resource Identifications, 1975-1980 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Grants - Ahrens, Dr. Edward H., Jr., 1955-1967 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Grants - American Pharmaceutical Manufacturing Award, 1945-1946 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Archibald NB 06895, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Ayala, 1967-1971 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Barron, Bruce, 1965-1971 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Mr. Bayless, 1959-1969 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Beam, Dr. Alexander G., 1956-1966 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Grants - Bernard, Dr. Rudy A., 1966-1969 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Grants - Bowan, Dr. Barbara, 1955-1967 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Grants - Brody, Stuart, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Grants - Brooks, Dr. Vernon, 1960-1964 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Grants - Brown - American Cancer Society, 1958-1970 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Grants - Brown - National Science Foundation, 1956-1970 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Grants - Caro, Dr. Lucien G., 1963-1966 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Grants - Chapeville, Dr. Francois, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Grants - Chase, Dr. Merril W., 1956-1961 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Grants - Dr. Costello, 1967-1969 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Grants - Craig, Dr. Lyman C., National Science Foundation + miscellaneous, 1957-1962 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Csapo, Dr. Appad I., 1959-1965 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Dales, Dr. Samuel, 1961-1968 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Davidson, 1966-1971 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Dobzhansky - Atomic Energy Commission, 1962-1965 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Dobzhansky, Theodosius, 1963-1972 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Doerfler, Watter, 1968-1971 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Grants - Dr. Dziewiatkowski, 1963-1967 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Grants - Edelman, NSF, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Edmundson, Allen B., 1959-1965 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Ford Foundation Grant to Hospital, 1955-1957 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Dr. Frankfurt, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Franzl, Dr. Robert E., 1961-1965 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Frenster, Dr. John, 1961-1965 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Goebel, Dr. Walther F., 1959-1971 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Grants - Gottschall, Dr. Gertrude Y., 1958-1962 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Grants - Granick, 1956-1966 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Grants - Gray, Jeffrey A., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Grants - Dr. Grafstein, 1965-1968 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Grants - Gregory, Dr. John D., 1959-1970 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Grants - Griffin - NSF Dr. Grant, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Grants - Dr. Griffin, 1957-1968 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Grants - Dr. Hartline - U.S. Navy, 1956-1967 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Held, Abraham A., 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Hirsch, Dr. James G., 1956-1975 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Holman, Dr. Halsted R., 1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Hotchkiss NSF, 1960-1971 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Jersaitis, Dr. Margeris A., 1958-1970 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Kaplan, Dr. Ann, 1963-1965 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Grants - Dr. Kunkel - Arthritis & Rheumatism Foundation, 1961-1963 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Grants - Koshland, Dr. Daniel E., 1960-1963 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Grants - Lancefield, Dr. Rebecca C., 1958-1963 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Grants - Lee, Johanna, 1957-1967 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Grants - Levey, Dr. Martin, 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Grants - Lorente, Dr. Rafael, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Grants - Lucas, Lenard, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Grants - Lunger, 1963-1966 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Grants - Lynch - American Cancer Society, 1958-1964 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Grants - McGinnis, Dr. Duncan A., 1957-1965 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Magdoff, Dr. Beatrice, 1962-1967 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Maguire, Henry C. Jr., 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Maramarasch, Dr. Karl, 1961-1965 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Merrifield, 1959-1967 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Miller, George, 1968-1970 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Miroff, Dr. George, 1960-1969 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Grants - Mirsky, Christmas Lectures, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Grants - Moore, Dr. Dan H., 1960-1964 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Grants - Moore, Dr. Dan H.-Office of Naval Research, 1957-1965 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Grants - Moore, Dr. Dan H.-Public Health Services, 1961-1966 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Grants - Moore, Dr. Stanford - Army Contract, 1960-1965 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Grants - Moore, Dr. Stanford - Stein, Dr. William H., 1956-1957 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Grants - Dr. Muller - Eberhard, Hans J., 1961-1966 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Grants - Murphy, Edward J., 1957-1963 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Grants - Prof. Nachmansohn, Columbia University Symposium at Rhode Island, 1958 September 25-30 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Naf, Dr. Ulrich, 1960-1962 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Nelson, Dr. John B., 1962-1968 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Nemethy, George, 1966-1968 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Grants - NTU, Dr. Man - Chiang, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Ogata, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Palade, 1959-1966 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Grants - Payne, Roger S., 1966-1968 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Grants - Pelletier, Dr. S. William, 1955-1962 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Grants - Perlmann, Gertrude E., 1956 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Grants - Perlmann, Gertrude E., 1964-1971 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Grants - Peterson, Dr. Malcolm L., 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Grants - Pierce, Dr. Cynthia, 1960-1964 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Grants - Pogo, A. O., 1965-1967 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Grants - Porter, Dr. Keith R., 1955-1961 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Grants - Rasmussen, Dr. Howard, 1957-1963 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Grants - Dr. Reddi, 1964-1971 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Grants - Robbins, Dr. William J., 1965-1970 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Rosenberg, Dr. Murray, 1962-1965 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Rothschild, Dr. Joel A., 1959-1973 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Rous, Dr. Peyton, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Rowlands, 1964-1966 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Ryan, James W., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Schneider, Dr. Howard A., 1957-1965 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Grants - Seuffert, Wolf D., 1966 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Grants - Shope, Dr. Richard E., 1957-1961 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Grants - Shedlovsky, Dr. Theodore, 1956-1964 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Grants - Song, Dr. Chull S., 1969 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Grants - Spritz, Norton, 1966-1969 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Grants - Stewart, John M., 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Grants - Stoeckenius, Dr. Walther, 1959-1967 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Grants - Dr. Bella S. Strauss, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Grants - Struhsaker, Thomas T., 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Grants - Sullivan, James, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Grants - Tamm - National Foundation, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Grants - Trager, 1956-1969 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Grants - Uziel, Dr. Mayo, 1955-1956 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Von Ehrenstein, Dr. G., 1960 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Weibel, Dr. Ewald, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Weiss, Dr. Paul - American Cancer Society, 1956-1962 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Woodford, 1965-1971 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Woolley, miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Dr. Donald Young - Russell Sage Foundation, 1965-1969 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Graphic Services, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Graphic Services, 1969-1974 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Graphic Services Final Balances, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Graphic Services, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Graphic Services (CES Working Files), 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Graphic Services, 1976-1980 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Griffi's Faculty Club, NYH-CUMC, 1971-1977 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Griffiths, Raymond B., 1974 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Gulf, 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Richard B. Harding, Jr., 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Health Care Plan, 1970-1980 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - H. E. W.- (Department of Health, Education and Welfare), University of the New York State - Education Department Higher Education Acts, Tiltles I and Via, 1963-1969 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - H. E. W. University of the State of New York - Education Department, Bureau of Statistical Services, 1967-1973 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Honorary Doctorates (CES Working Files), 1975 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Housing Committee, 1968-1972 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Housing Committee, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - General Housing Information, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - General Housing Information, 1969-1978 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Housing - Individual matters, filed alphabetically, 1970-1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Housing Sub - Committee, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Hospital, 1931 1956-1977 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Hospital - Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1974-1977 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - RU Hospital - Utilization Review, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - RU Hospital - Memorial Hospital, 1974-1976 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Hospital - Methadone Maintenance, 1970-1975 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - HUD Material, 1971-1973 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - HUD Material, 1970-1973 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - HUD Material, 1971-1973 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - I. D. Card Procedure Updated, 1969-1973 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - "In Search of Fever", 2nd draft script (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - IBM, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Informal Survey of Internal Communications within the Rockefeller University, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Inquiries to Dormitory, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - International Research Centers, 1968-1971 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Biomedical Research, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Muscle Disease proposed affiliation with Rockefeller University, 1967-1973 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Instrument Shop, 1960-1976 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Insurance Company, 1972-1976 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Interinstitutional Community Computer Task Force, 1969-1971 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Interinstitutional Computer Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Institutional Coordinating Group, 1973-1977 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Invoices, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Invoices, 1972-1976 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Contract - Ira H. Hardin Co., Inc., 1976 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Iran II, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Iran Articles, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Iran correspondence incoming, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Iran correspondence, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Iran feasibility study, 1974-1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Iran - Interviews and comments, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Iran, final report to, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Iran and Institutions, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Iran - memoranda, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Iranian Research Center, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Isotope Laboratories, 1961-1978 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Susann Jacqueline Cancer Research Fund, 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Janitorial Services Report, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Japan, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Job Classification Index and Salary Progression Schedule, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Journals - Budget Proposal Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Journal of Cell Biology Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Journals of Cell Biology - budget, 1963-1975 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Journal of Clinical Investigation - Paul Weiss, 1969-1974 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Journal of Experimental Medicine, 1969-1973 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Journals - General Information, 1968-1979 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Journal of General Physiology, 1968-1975 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Journals - JCI Neurosciences volumes (Journals of Clinical Investigation), 1968-1970 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Journal of Lipid Research, 1969-1971 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Journals - Order Service, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Journals - Overhead, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Judicial Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Judicial Committee Working File (CES Working File), 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Junior Faculty Meetings, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - The Kellogg Foundation, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Kilham, Beder & Chu - regarding Welch Hall library facilities, 1972-1974 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Klingenstein, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Kobler, John - FS Draft on the RU (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Kobler, John, 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Kobler, John - Case Statement, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Kraft, George, 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Kresge Foundation, 1971-1975 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Lab and AARH Renovations, 1972-1973 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Landscaping, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Laundry, 1969-1976 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Le Sueur, Charles Robin, 1972-1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Lease - Faculty House, 1975-1977 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Lecture Series - General Files, 1970-1973 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Legal Services, 1975-1978 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Lenox Hills Neighborhood Association, 1972-1978 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Library, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Library, 1968-1970 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Library, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Library, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Library, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Library, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Library, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Library, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Library, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Library Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Library Committee of the Associated Medical Schools of New York and New Jersey, 1972-1973 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Library Research, 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Library Survey of Periodicals Collection, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Library Users Committee, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Library Working File, 1973-1976 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Library - Students, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Library, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Lyman, Craig, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Listings, 1954-1973 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Loans, 1973-1976 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Logan, Jonathon, 1972-1973 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - MacInnes Cottage, 1969-1980 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Magie, Lila J. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Management Agreement - Faculty House, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Management Conferences, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Management Conferences - Committee for Economic Development, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Manoussoff: Queensborough Bridge, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Markle Foundation, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Mass Spectrometry Laboratory, 1973-1977 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Max C. Fleischmann Foundation, 1972-1975 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - McGinnity, T. P. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - McNamara, William E., 1968-1971 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Meal and Board Plan, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Media and Glassware Services, 1970-1977 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Medical Library Center (CES Working File), 1959-1976 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Meid, Don, 1971-1972 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Memorandum to Dr. Frederick Seitz and Dr. Albert Gold "The Energy Status at the Rockefeller University", 1977 February 14 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Chapel - Memorial Hall (Fund Proposal), 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Methadane Data Processing, 1972-1975 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Microanalytical Service, 1971-1972 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Microprocessor - Biotechnology Resource Committee, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Microprocessor Proposal, 1976-1978 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - 500 East 63rd - Legal Papers, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Miller, Neal: Report on Laboratory, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Millbrook - Innisfree Foundation - Cary Trust, 1971-1975 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Mirsky, Sonia W. (I) (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Mirsky, Sonia W. (I) (Box 59, Folder 4A)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    File was initially closed until April 24, 2012. The material is now open for scholarly research.
  - Mirsky, Sonia W. (II) (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - re: Mrs. Mirsky, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1969-1972 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous II, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966-1973 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Mitchell Lama Act, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Mobil Oil Corporation, 1973-1975 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Monthly Commentary D. J. Lyons, 1970 August-1971 April (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Monthly Commentary D. J. Lyons, 1971 May-October (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Monthly Commentary, 1971 November-???? June (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Multiple Sclerosis, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Munroe, Warren H., 1970-1974 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Museum, 1974-1975 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - NAS National Academy of Sciences papers regarding move into the Joseph Henry building, 1967-1969 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - National Distillers, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - National Science Policy Proposal, 1970-1972 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Neurosciences booklet, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Neurosciences program, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - New England Institute, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - New York City Regional Plan for Higher Education, 1971; 1 of 2 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - New York City Regional Plan for Higher Education, 1972-1975; 2 of 2 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - New York State Education Department - news, 1971-1978 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - New York State Education Services Corporation, 1969-1977 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - New York University: Proposed Affiliation with the Rockefeller University, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - News Coverage (subway), 1976-1977 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Nichols - Century Club, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Nichols - Cosmos Club, 1972-1973 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Nichols, Rodney W. (I), 1974-1978 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Nichols, Rodney W. (II), 1969-1974 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Non Faculty Personnel Report, 1970-1971 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    Folder is closed until April 24, 2012.
  - Objective Milestone Network, undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - O'Donnel, John J. (I), 1973-1976 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - O'Donnel, John J., 1957-1967 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - O'Donnel, John J., 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - O'Donnel, John J., 1970 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - O'Donnel, John J., 1971 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - O'Donnel, John J., 1972-1974 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - O'Donnel, John J. (II), 1975-1978 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Office Space - Library - Alterations, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - On Campus Housing Agreement, 1972-1975 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Open House Program, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Operation and Maintenance - FY'75, 1971-1974 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Orientation Lectures, 1958-1968 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Outline Specifications, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - The Palade Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Park Area for Children of University Personnel (request), 1971 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Parking, 1975-1978 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Parking Analysis - Monthly Report, 1970-1976 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Parking - General - File I, 1968-1972 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Parking - General - File II, 1973-1975 March (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Parking - General - File II, 1975 April-1976 May (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Parking on 68th Street, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Payson, 1975 December 3 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Penndorf, Paul R., 1969-1978 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Higher Education Agency, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Periodical Collection, 1971-1978 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Personnel Matters - General, 1969-1978 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Matters - Individual, 1970-1976 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Papers filed in alphabetical order.
  - Personnel: Requisitions for lab personnel, 1970-1971 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - The Philip D. McMaster Basic Research Fund, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Philosophy Program, 1969-1975 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Photo and Directory, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Physical and Financial Conditions of NYH - Cornell Medical Center A Program for Action (includes Appendix), 1972 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Pinkertons, Inc: Security Guards, 1970-1971 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Pipe Bomb Explosion - Petition, 1970 May 28 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Pipe Bomb Explosion - Clippings, 1970 May 28 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Planning General, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Policy Document and Reports, 1970-1977 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Political Action Activities - Board Statements, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Political Action Activities - Committee of Twelve, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Political Action Activities - Committee for Democratic Society, 1965-1968 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Political Action Activities - Correspondence from outside RU, 1970-1971 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Political Action Activities - Department of St.: Section 706 of Public Law 91-153 regarding unrest, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Political Action Activities - Faculty Correspondence, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Political Action Activities - General, 1969-1972 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Political Action Activities - General Matters, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Political Action Activities - Gene Kone and Outside Press, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Political Action Activities - News and Notes, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Political Action Activities - "The Newspapers", Strike calls, etc., 1968-1970 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Political Action Activities - President's Commission on Campus Unrest, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Political Action Activities - Princeton Plan, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Political Action Activities - Signs and Posters, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 7)